Kamil Vavra, Application Security Engineer

 $Czech\ Republic, vavkamil@protonmail.com$

LINKS	LinkedIn, Personal Blog, GitHub, HackerOne, Bugcrowd, Twitter, Reddit, PentesterLab		
PROFILE	I have been an ethical hacker since early childhood. Nowadays, I specialize mainly in offensing Constantly researching new attack vectors, solving challenges, and improving my skillset is a of my everyday life and passion.		
EMPLOYMENT HISTORY			
Jun 2019 — Present	Application Security Engineer, Kiwi.com	Brno	
	 Improved, stabilized, and managed a successful bug bounty program Established Secure Development Lifecycle, with focus on education & SAST Automated tedious security tasks, SDL, and vulnerability management Executed penetration tests, vulnerability scans, and continuous threats research Performed manual code reviews of critical services Introduced company-wide Rate Limiting & Web Application Firewall Contributed to long term security strategy and objectives 		
Jul 2020 — Present	Penetration Tester, TunaSec z.s.	Brno	
	 Set the foundation for our non-profit organization Delivered penetration tests for various clients Wrote numerous blog posts about security & privacy 		
Jun 2020 — Nov 2020	Lector of Ethical Hacking, ENGETO s.r.o.	Brno	
	 Created intermediate Ethical Hacking course for IT staff Delivered virtual & on-premise trainings during the coronavirus crisis 		
Oct 2018 — May 2019	IT Security Assessment Specialist, Home Credit International a.s.	Brno	
	 Performed assessments in companies of Home Credit Group and Air Bank (PPF Group Responsible for Web Application Penetration Testing Conducted Software Security & Compliance Reviews (ISO 27001) Delivered Internal Security Audits & formalized Security Processes)	
Apr 2017 — Mar 2019	IT Security Researcher, SYSYstems, s.r.o.	Svitavy	
Dec 2017 — Feb 2019	Ethical Hacker, WebAlert.cz	Svitavy	
Jan 2016 — Dec 2016	Bug Bounty Hunter, Bugcrowd Inc.	Svitavy	
Feb 2014 — Aug 2016	Network Administrator, Mendel University	Brno	
Jul 2009 — Feb 2014	IT Freelancer, Self employed	Svitavy	
Jun 2011 — May 2013	System Administrator, MACHALA GROUP SE	Svitavy	
Jun 2010 — May 2011	IT Specialist, Machala a.s.	Svitavy	
EDUCATION			
Sep 2006 — Jun 2010	Informatics in Economy, VDA.cz High School Diploma	Česká Třebová	

SKILLS	Application Security Penetration Testing		Offensive Web Security Secure Code Review		
LANGUAGES	Czech	Native speaker	English	C1	
CERTIFICATIONS					
May 2021	Burp Suite Certified Practitioner			PortSwigger	
	I was the first person in the world who successfully passed the certification.				
	• https://portswigger.net	:/web-security/e/c/d1af2e	3f879e4c25		
COURSES					
	Advanced Web Attacks and Exploitation (AWAE), Offensive Security				
	Code Review Badge, Pe	ntesterLab			
VULNERABILITIES					
	CVE-2021-44223				
		ln/detail/CVE-2021-4422			

REFERENCES

Web Security Academy

CVE-2020-26297

I'm currently in the top 10 best-ranked hackers in the Portswigger's Hall Of Fame

• https://portswigger.net/web-security/hall-of-fame

• https://nvd.nist.gov/vuln/detail/CVE-2020-26297

OWASP Czech Chapter

I'm a regular speaker at every OWASP Czech Chapter meeting

• https://vavkamil.cz/talks/

r/bugbounty

I'm a lead moderator of bug bounty subreddit, responsible for a community of \sim 17k members

• https://www.reddit.com/r/bugbounty/

GitHub open-source

 $Open-source\ code\ is\ my\ passion,\ I\ main maintain tant\ a\ couple\ of\ popular\ security\ oriented\ projects$

• https://github.com/vavkamil

Personal blog

I love sharing my knowledge with the community and regularly publish research on my blog

• https://vavkamil.cz/